Finding aid to the Classes of 1891-1900 records CA.MS.01022
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1897 Records, 1893-1967; 20.062 linear feet (39 containers)
  - Songs, 1893-1897 (Box 1526, Folder 6)
  - Sophomore Receptions, 1893 (Box 1526, Folder 7)
  - Sophomore-Senior Reception for 1895 (Box 1526, Folder 8)
  - Student Rooms, undated (Box 1526, Folder 9)
  - Class Supper, 1897 (Box 1526, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1895-1958 (Box 1526, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 1526, Folder 12)
  - "Weep", 1894 (Box 1526, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1912-1962 (Box 1527, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Bulletin, 1918-1927 (Box 1527, Folder 2)
  - Reunion, 1898 (Box 1527, Folder 3)
  - Reunion, 190 (Box 1527, Folder 4)
  - Reunion, 1907-1910 (Box 1527, Folder 5)
  - Reunion, 1907 (Box 1527, Folder 6)
  - Reunion, 1912 (Box 1527, Folder 7)
  - Reunion, 1917 (Box 1527, Folder 8)
  - Reunion, 1922 (Box 1527, Folder 9)
  - Reunion, 1932 (Box 1528, Folder 1)
  - Reunion, 1937 (Box 1528, Folder 2)
  - Reunion, 1942 (Box 1528, Folder 3)
  - Reunion, 1947 (Box 1528, Folder 4)
  - Reunion, 1950 (Box 1528, Folder 5)
  - Reunion, 1952 (Box 1528, Folder 6)
  - Reunion, 1957 (Box 1528, Folder 7)
  - Reunion, 1962-1967 (Box 1528, Folder 8)
  - Reunion Memorabilia, undated (Box 1528, Folder 9)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1528, Folder 10)
  - Senior Dramatics: The Merchant of Venice (Box 1529, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1897 (Box 1529, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1897 (Box 1529, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1897 (Box 1529, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1897 (Box 1529, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1897 (Box 1529, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics: Prompt Book, 1897 (Box 1529.1, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics: Prompt Book and Clippings, 1897 (Box 1529.1, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics: Stage Properties Book, 1897 (Box 1529.1, Folder 3)
  - Memorabilia (Box 1529.2)
  - Individuals A-B (Box 1530)
  - Individuals C-D (Box 1531)
  - Individuals F (Box 1532)
  - Individuals G-J (Box 1533)
  - Individuals K-Mi (Box 1534)
  - Individuals Mo-P (Box 1534.1)
  - Individuals Ph-Se (Box 1535)
  - Individuals Sh-Sz (Box 1536)
  - Tallant, Alice Weld (Memorabilia Book) (Box 1537)
  - Individuals T-Z (Box 1537.1)
  - Atwater, Helen Woodward (Box 1538)
  - Bissell, Eleanor M. (photo albums) (Box 1538.1)
  - Bissell, Eleanor M. (scrapbook) (Box 1539)
  - Branch, Anna Hempstead (Box 1540)
  - Coe, Margaret Elmer (Photo Album) (Box 1551.4)
  - Cutler, (Harriet) Isabelle (scrapbook) (Box 1541)
  - Cutler, (Harriet) Isabelle (scrapbook) (Box 1541.1)
  - Dodge, Ellen (photo albums) (Box 1542)
  - Fuller, Mae Rawson (photo albums) (Box 1542.1)
  - Hale, Franc Wales (photo album, scrapbook) (Box 1545)
  - Hersom, Mabel (scrapbook) (Box 1543.1)
  - Hunt, Agnes (scrapbook, photo album) (Box 1544)
  - Jeffrey, Agnes (photo album) (Box 1542.1)
  - Jeffrey, Agnes (scrapbook) (Box 1544.1)
  - Jeffrey, Agnes (memorabilia book) (Box 1544.2)
  - Jeffrey, Agnes (friendship calendar) (Box 1545)
  - Johnson, Mary Hooker (photo album) (Box 1545)
  - Kennard, Helen May (correspondence) (Box 1546)
  - Kennard, Helen May (scrapbook, typescript of correspondence) (Box 1547)
  - Smith, Mary Bartlett (Box 1543)
  - Tallant, Alice Weld (scrapbook) (Box 1548)
  - Townsend, Therina (photo album, misc., class notes) (Box 1549)
  - Vermilye, Jane Thomas (photo albums) (Box 1550)
  - Vermilye, Jane Thomas (photo album) (Box 1545)
  - Wiard, Grace Louise (correspondence) (Box 1551)
  - Wilkinson, Katharine May (scrapbook) (Box 1541.1)
  - Wyman, Edith Johnson (photo album) (Box 1551.1)
  - Unidentified (photo album) (Box 1542.1)
- Class of 1898 Records, 1894-1969; 9.5 linear feet (19 containers)
  The Class of 1898 was the twentieth entering class and the twentieth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1898 records, 1894-1969, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1898, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, correspondences, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 1)
  - Bookplate, 1939 (Box 1552, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 5)
  - Essay Prize Committee, undated (Box 1552, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind by 1897, 1894 (Box 1552, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1894-1898 (Box 1552, Folder 8)
  - History, 1898-1905 (Box 1552, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 11)
  - Junior Prom, 1897 (Box 1552, Folder 12)
  - Junior Reception, 1897 (Box 1552, Folder 13)
  - Junior Ushers, 1897 (Box 1552, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1924-1958 (Box 1552, Folder 15)
  - Reunion, 1899 (Box 1553, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1900 (Box 1553, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1903 (Box 1553, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1908 (Box 1553, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1913 (Box 1553, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1918 (Box 1553, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1923 (Box 1553, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1928 (Box 1553, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1933 (Box 1553, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1938 (Box 1553, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1943 (Box 1553, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 1553, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1950 (Box 1553, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1953 (Box 1553, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 1553, Folder 15)
  - Reunion Correspondence, 1963 (Box 1553, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 1553, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 1553, Folder 18)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1553, Folder 19)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1894 (Box 1553, Folder 20)
  - Sophomore-Senior Entertainment, 1896 (Box 1553, Folder 21)
  - Class Supper, 1898 (Box 1553, Folder 22)
  - Songs, 1894-1898 (Box 1553, Folder 23)
  - Student Rooms, undated (Box 1553, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbook, 1894-1898 (Box 1554)
  - Scrapbook, 1894-1898 (Box 1554)
  - Reunion Guest book, 1898-1963 (Box 1554)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 4)
  - Memorabilia (Box 1555.1)
  - Individuals A-C (Box 1556)
  - Individuals D-J (Box 1557)
  - Individuals K-Mc (Box 1558)
  - Individuals Mi-Sc (Box 1559)
  - Individuals Se-Z (Box 1560)
  - Collins, Rejoyce Ballance (scrapbook) (Box 1567.1)
  - Daskam, Josephine Dodge (post grad) (Box 1561)
  - Esterbrook, Edith Marsh (scrapbook) (Box 1562)
  - Fast, Louisa Kimball (scrapbook, photo album, misc.) (Box 1563)
  - Fast, Louisa Kimball (class notebooks, correspondence, misc.) (Box 1564)
  - Gower, Ethel Margaret (photo album) (Box 1565)
  - Graham, Bertha Ellen (photo album) (Box 1565)
  - Lovejoy, Deborah Eliza (photo album) (Box 1567.2)
  - MacAlister, Julia Clyde (photo album) (Box 1567.2)
  - Padgham, Estella Elizabeth (photo albums) (Box 1567.2)
  - Seelye, Henrietta Sheldon (scrapbooks) (Box 1566)
  - Todd, Alice Adele (photo albums) (Box 1567)
  - Wheeler, Lucia May (photo album) (Box 1567.2)
  - Wing, Adeline Flint (photo albums) (Box 1567)
- Class of 1899 Records, 1895-1964; 13.167 linear feet (21 containers)
  The Class of 1899 was the twenty-first entering class and the twenty-first graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1899 records, 1895-1964, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1899, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 1)
  - Collation, undated (Box 1568, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photos, 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Grind by 1898, 1895 (Box 1568, Folder 6)
  - Groups Photos, 1895-1899 (Box 1568, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 8)
  - Ivy Day, 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1899 (Box 1568, Folder 10)
  - Junior Prom, 1898 (Box 1568, Folder 11)
  - Letters, 1914-1956 (Box 1568, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1568, Folder 13)
  - Reunion, 1900 (Box 1568, Folder 14)
  - Reunion, 1901 (Box 1568, Folder 15)
  - Reunion, 1904 (Box 1568, Folder 16)
  - Reunion, 1909 (Box 1568, Folder 17)
  - Reunion, 1910 (Box 1568, Folder 18)
  - Reunion, 1914 (Box 1568, Folder 19)
  - Reunion, 1919 (Box 1569, Folder 1)
  - Reunion, 1924 (Box 1569, Folder 2)
  - Reunion, 1929 (Box 1569, Folder 3)
  - Reunion, 1934 (Box 1569, Folder 4)
  - Reunion, 1939 (Box 1569, Folder 5)
  - Reunion, 1944 (Box 1569, Folder 6)
  - Reunion, 1949 (Box 1569, Folder 7)
  - Reunion, 1954 (Box 1569, Folder 8)
  - Reunion, 1959 (Box 1569, Folder 9)
  - Reunion, 1964 (Box 1569, Folder 10)
  - Secretary's Notebook, 1895-1954 (Box 1569, Folder 11)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1569, Folder 12)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1895 (Box 1569, Folder 13)
  - Sophomore-Senior Entertainment for 1897 (Box 1569, Folder 14)
  - Student Rooms, undated (Box 1569, Folder 15)
  - Class Supper, 1899 (Box 1569, Folder 16)
  - Senior Dramatics Clippings, 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photograph Album, 1899 (Box 1571, Folder 5)
  - Banner (Box 1568.1)
  - Individuals A-Cha (Box 1572)
  - Individuals Che-Chu (Box 1573)
  - Individuals Cl-H (Box 1574)
  - Individuals K-R (Box 1575)
  - Individuals S-Z (Box 1575.1)
  - Allen, Abby Louise (photo album) (Box 1575.2)
  - Bell, Caroline Stowell (photo album) (Box 1575.5)
  - Bliss, Harriet Chalmers (scrapbook) (Box 1576)
  - Bouve, Stella (photo album) (Box 1575.2)
  - Brackett, Georgianna May (photo album) (Box 1580.1)
  - Burrage, Edith May(photo album) (Box 1575.2)
  - Choate, Miriam Foster (scrapbook) (Box 1577)
  - Criley, Katherine May (photo albums) (Box 1575.5)
  - Dering, Charlotte Ray (photo albums) (Box 1577.1)
  - Goldsmith, Gertrude Brown (class notes and misc.) (Box 1578)
  - Hills, Jane Reed (photo albums) (Box 1575.3)
  - Kennard, Mary (scrapbook) (Box 1580.2)
  - Klock, Eunice Pearl (scrapbook) (Box 1575.4)
  - Lyman, (Mary) Alice (scrapbook) (Box 1579)
  - Marcy, Annie Maude (photo album) (Box 1580.1)
  - Wiggin, Deborah Allen (scrapbook) (Box 1580)
- Class of 1900 Records, 1896-1969; 9.0 linear feet (18 containers)
  The Class of 1900 was the twenty-second entering class and the twenty-second graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1900 records, 1896-1965, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1900, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, photo albums, and other memorabilia.
  - Class Baby, 1915-1922 (Box 1581, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate, 1900 (Box 1581, Folder 2)
  - Clipping Book from Smith Alumnae Quarterly, 1922-1948 (Box 1581, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1900 (Box 1581, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1900 (Box 1581, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1900 (Box 1581, Folder 6)
  - Class Day, 1900 (Box 1581, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Grind by 1899, 1896 (Box 1581, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1896-1900 (Box 1581, Folder 9)
  - Class History, 1897-1900 (Box 1581, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1900 (Box 1581, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1900 (Box 1581, Folder 12)
  - Junior Frolic, 1899 (Box 1581, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1899 (Box 1581, Folder 14)
  - Junior Prom Programs, 1899 (Box 1581, Folder 15)
  - Junior-Senior Entertainment, 1899 (Box 1581, Folder 16)
  - Junior Ushers, 1899 (Box 1581, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1916-1962 (Box 1581, Folder 18)
  - Place Cards and Tabs, undated (Box 1581, Folder 19)
  - Class Ribbon, 1950 (Box 1582, Folder 1)
  - Seal, Emblem, Stationery, etc, undated (Box 1582, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary- Correspondence, 1969; 1951; 1934 (Box 1582, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary- Minutes, 1896-1960 (Box 1582, Folder 4)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1582, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1896 (Box 1582, Folder 6)
  - Class Supper, 1900 (Box 1582, Folder 7)
  - Class Treasurer, 1950-1960 (Box 1582, Folder 8)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1900 (Box 1582.1, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs (Box 1582.1, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photograph Album, 1900 (Box 1582.1, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photograph Album, 1900 (Box 1582.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1583, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1583, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1901-1903 (Box 1583, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1910 (Box 1583, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1915 (Box 1583, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1920 (Box 1583, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1925 (Box 1583, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 1583, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 1583, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 1583, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1945 (Box 1583, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1950 (Box 1583, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 1583, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 1583, Folder 14)
  - Reunion Register, 1920-1940 (Box 1583, Folder 15)
  - Individuals A-F (Box 1584)
  - Individuals G-L (Box 1585)
  - Individuals M-Tu (Box 1586)
  - Individuals U-Z (Box 1586.1)
  - Baldwin, Ella Mabel (Botany notebook) (Box 1587)
  - Butler, Irene Livingston (memorabilia book) (Box 1588)
  - Emery, Emma Darling (scrapbook) (Box 1589)
  - Janney, Helen Mary (photo album) (Box 1591.1)
  - Leavens, Faith Robinson (memorabilia book and photo album) (Box 1591.3)
  - Loheed, Bertha Miriam (scrapbook) (Box 1591.2)
  - Meier, Elizabeth Porter (memorabilia book) (Box 1591.4)
  - Mitchell, Leslie (photo albums) (Box 1591.3)
  - Monson, Edith Dale (Photograph Album) (Box 1591.5)
  - Sanderson, Sarah Watson (memorabilia book) (Box 1590)
  - Smith, Anna Jaffray (memorabilia book) (Box 1591)
  - Weil, Margaret Adelaide (photo albums) (Box 1591.4)
  - Unidentified (photo album) (Box 1591.4)